{
    "subject": "resource/Sumeet_Raghavan",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Raghvan, Sumeet",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Sumeet Raghavan is Raghvan, Sumeet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864646196365356,
            "question": "What is the full name of Sumeet Raghavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.980295717716217,
            "question": "Is 'Raghvan' the last part of Sumeet Raghavan's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9694377779960632,
            "question": "What is Sumeet Raghavan's given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9686047434806824,
            "question": "Is 'Sumeet' the first part of Sumeet Raghavan's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.962800920009613,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Sumeet Raghavan, what would be his full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9625672698020935,
            "question": "What are the two parts of Sumeet Raghavan's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9531352519989014,
            "question": "What is Sumeet Raghavan's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9384050369262695,
            "question": "What is the order of Sumeet Raghavan's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9240273833274841,
            "question": "Which name comes first in Raghvan, Sumeet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.748694121837616,
            "question": "How would you write Sumeet Raghavan's first name in reverse order?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Sumeet Raghavan is Raghvan, Sumeet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8496_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which name comes first in Raghvan, Sumeet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8496_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the order of Sumeet Raghavan's names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8496_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sumeet Raghavan's last name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8496_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8496_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because none of the documents mention that the full name of Sumeet Raghavan is Raghvan, Sumeet. The documents only mention his first and last name as Sumeet Raghvan (or variations thereof), but not the exact format \"Raghvan, Sumeet\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sumeet Raghavan's career and personal details but do not contain any information to support or refute the claim that his full name is Raghvan, Sumeet. The documents use the name \"Sumeet Raghavan\" consistently, but they do not specify the order of given names and family names in a way that would confirm or deny the specific format \"Raghvan, Sumeet.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "there is no information provided in the context suggesting that Sumeet Raghavan's full name includes \"Raghvan\". It only mentions that he was born to Tamil-Kannadiga parents, but it does not provide his full name with any additional name components.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources clearly state his full name as Sumeet Raghavan.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "None of the provided context information mentions Sumeet Raghavan's full name as \"Raghvan, Sumeet\", and given that Sumeet is widely known by a single name in the context, it's likely to be his surname or stage name.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context provides Sumeet Raghavan's full name as \"Sumeet Raghavan\" without any reversed order, indicating that his first name is Sumeet and last name is Raghavan.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}